<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <packageId>jecrell.rimwriter</packageId>
  <name>RimWriter - Books, Scrolls, Tablets, and Libraries</name>
  <author>Jecrell</author>
  <url>https://discord.gg/AaVFA7V</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>jecrell.jecstools</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>1.21.0.0 (04-06-2020)

Add tablets, books, scrolls and more to your RimWorld playthroughs.

RimWriter is a mod that adds a lot of content focused on writing to supplement the standard vanilla RimWorld playthrough such as:
-Items
  * Stone Tablets
  * Leather Scrolls
  * Journals
  * Handwritten Books
  * Typed Books and Journals
  * Skillbooks for improving skills

-Furniture
  * Stone shelves for tablets
  * Scrollcases, tall and short
  * Bookcases, tall and short
  * Writer's tables
  * A typewriter

-Features
  * Customized text generation for tablets, books, and journals.
  * Compatiblity with Lord of the Rims and Call of Cthulhu mods.
    - Writing reduces sanity loss over time.
    - Future compatability with storing Grimoires and Wizard textbooks inside bookcases/scrollcases.

Why create this mod?
I wanted to make a framework sort of mod that I could add to or use later in my current and future projects. I feel that tablets, scrolls, and books all have a clear place in RimWorld and future mods.

Thank you to my Patrons for supporting me in my efforts. Without you, none of this would be possible.

These are the most excellent rim dwellers who support me: 
Cade Perkinson, Jay Sacane, John Pahl, Tankok1998 also known as the Shermanlover, Vahl Kilmer, Zsolt Biró, Genaeve, JD2.0, Olteanu Laurentiu, Penelope Charli Whitman, Charlie Garnham, Steven Pretswell, Sultan Saltlick, RainerWingel, Daniel Paseka, Kyben, Charles Morris, Chris Seieroe, Robin Gleeson, Lea Stannard, Teres, David Silberstein, Kiya Nicoll, Matt Harris, Paul Fenwick, Michael Whitehead, Robert Alessi, Elodie, Gothi, Audrin Navarro, Михаил Юрченко, Calum, Tim Stillson, Populous25, Don Homer, Adam Bliss, Maaxar, Christopher, TinyFloatingTurtle, John Kanady, Midgeman, Nathan Getman, Sharp Spook, LionsFate, Cristina Shaver, Mark, George Chong Chuang Ming, Oliver White, roxxploxx, Emily Shaw, Justin Andres, Robin Hager, Kevin Reagan, Austin Harbert, Marcus Regan, E_T, Alex Mederer, Alexander, Toss Antilles

========================
Changelog
========================
1.21.0.0 (04-06-2020)
========================
Updated for RimWorld 1.1. Upscaled and redid textures to improve quality when using mods such as Camera plus.

1.20.0.2 (01-04-2019)
========================
Skillbooks now properly display graphics and authors

1.20.0.1 (10-30-2018)
========================
Fixes for potential XML errors from inheritence from other mods.

1.20.0.0 (10-26-2018)
========================
Available now for RimWorld 1.0.

</description>
</ModMetaData>